I ate seven pints of ice cream this week
and was still able to maintain a caloric
deficit. Here are the seven pints I ate
this week. Started off with a fish food
flavor, one of my all-time favorite Ben
& Jerry's flavors, chocolate ice cream,
chocolate chunks, marshmallows, and a
caramel drizzle. Then I did a DQ
recreation of their most popular
Blizzard, surprisingly, the turtle pecan
cluster. vanilla ice cream, chocolate
chips, some pecans, and some caramel on
top. Then I did a highly requested Ben &
Jerry's recreation, American dream,
vanilla ice cream with some
chocolatecovered waffle cones and some
caramel on top. This was honestly
phenomenal. Then I tried to make as low
calorie of a chocolate base as I could.
I used the milk 50 chocolate milk. Got
it down to 106 calories. still packs 17
grams of protein. Then we did a
chocolate chip. This is just an alltime
classic for me. I use my chocolate chip
hack to get the perfect creamy chocolate
chips. I have a video about that if you
want to check it out. And then we did a
chocolate chip cookie dough blizzard.
Again, recreating one of Dairy Queen's
most popular Blizzard flavors. This was
a vanilla base with little chocolate
chip cookies mixed in. And then I ended
off the week with a salted caramel
brownie sundae. The entire pint plus the
brownie plus the caramel was just 400
calories and packed almost 50 grams of
protein.